As we all travel across the sea,
raising our voices, we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to
go, everybody rejoices.
Now let's go, get the sails all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure,
we're itching to try.
Get ready to roam.
So all aboard now!
We're set to go.
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well, don't you think?
That sounds really fun!
All this excitement!
Second to none!
As we all travel across the sea!
Raising our voices!
We take in the beautiful blue world!
Our spirits ready to go!
Everybody rejoices!
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled!
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget!
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set!
Now I won't be scared!
As long as I keep that feeling there!
With that, let us keep up the pace!
While enjoying every
trip from place to place!
Our timid hearts get the rhythm and great!
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found!
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous!
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you now, fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Hey, you're back.
I thought you were too hurt to fight.
Did something happen?
You look a lot better now.
You really saved my life back there.
That was scary.
It's true.
I was seriously injured when I dragged
myself to the kitchen to acquire the salt,
but then something most
fortuitous happened.
I discovered some delicious milk,
which I promptly consumed,
thus recovering my health.
Calcium doesn't act that fast. Come on!
So there you have it, everyone.
Milk can heal your broken bones! Lair!
Anyway, we have the salt we need now.
This should be enough to purify that
giant, but it might be a close call.
And speaking of close calls, it
looks like the kitchen's blocked off.
In other words, we only
get one chance to do this.
We don't have much time.
Let's move it.
If we don't want to melt when the
sun rises, we have two objectives.
We're gonna feed the salt to that
monster, and we gotta beat Moria.
You wanted a chance to get
your shadows back from me.
Well, here I am.
Go ahead and try.
But I'll warn you, I'm more than
just a passenger, nor a stomach.
When I'm done with you, you'll
wish you'd melted away in the sun.
I'll show you what real
nightmares are made of!
Thank you for this chance, Straw Hats.
I swear that I shall fight beside
you with every ounce of my might.
Although this small
gesture scarcely repays
the debt I owe you for
recovering my shadow,
I shall offer what assistance I can.
Now let's go!
Ouch.
We don't need you breaking any more bones,
so just hold on to the
salt and take it easy.
I got a few tricks up my sleeves.
Let's try my anti-monster shells.
All right, pal.
If my last shot was too small, try this.
Franky, are you ready?
We're gonna light this zombie
up with my special oil star.
Sweet.
Here I go.
Ignite!
Supersize...
Firebird star!
You'll be fine.
Don't let a little fire get to you.
Those feelings of pain are
nothing but lingering memories.
From back when you were
alive, it's all in your head.
Zombies don't have to worry
about any of that nonsense.
Just calm down and put out the fire.
You'll see.
This is our chance, Zoro. Come on! Got it.
All right, green sword style!
Great Buddha Duck!
My turn, Jango Cannon!
Take this!
It's coming straight at us!
Vente Floor should do the trick.
Damn it! No fair!
He's using our own attacks against us!
Sorry about that, you guys okay?
Hold my new weapon, the Stern Beetle!
Hell yeah!
I'm ready whenever you are!
Just a word of warning, I haven't
had a chance to test this thing,
so I don't know what will
happen when I let it loose!
You think I can't handle this, bro?
I'm extra super this week.
I got it under control.
All right, then get in. Roger.
Shoot me straight into that
thing's stomach, and we got this.
Special attack.
Iron Man's coming.
Nice.
Now this is some super speed.
Get ready.
This border cannon of
mine was specially made
to take down sea kings and jerks like you.
I'm going to wipe that slug
grin right off your face, Moria!
I keep forgetting he's so fast.
He might not look like him, but
he's got Luffy's moves for sure.
Franky, no! Oh!
Please, don't die!
Don't stop now, Oz.
That was a nice shot, but
I'm afraid he's still alive.
Why don't you stop on him?
Okay.
Ooh!
Dammit, he's gonna finish him off!
Stop!
He can't even move!
Thunderbolt!
Look, that cloud!
Tempo!
Nice shot, but where did it come from?
Lightning, it has to be her.
That's the climb attack.
Don't know where she is, but Nami's fine.
What was that flash? Was it lightning?
Oh, frightening.
That must have been Orr's.
I mean, he can do anything, right?
There she is.
It's Nami.
Could you stop yelling already?
Now they're going to know where I am.
She yelled at me.
Just like old times.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Yell at me more, Nami.
I'm so sorry I couldn't save you.
You can tell me I'll
screw what I am all right.
Would you shut up?
It's the gun!
See, I told you!
Gun-gun!
Huh?
Wait, he's not going to stretch, is he?
I mean, Danny?
It shouldn't reach her, right?
Usopp, hurry!
You've got to get Franky out of here!
Right!
It's the gun!
What?
He stretched! Impossible!
It worked!
That was new, but it doesn't feel new.
You've got to be kidding me!
No!
Look, up there!
She's okay!
She sure is screaming a lot,
but at least Robin caught her.
That was certainly a surprise.
You're not hurt, are you?
No, just shaking up.
Thank you.
I don't get it, but I
know it can't be good.
Two people can't have the
same Devil Fruit power.
Even if he has Luffy's shadow,
he shouldn't be able to do that.
It's Moria.
Must have been one of his tricks.
I'm gonna kill that guy.
Now come, go!
Well, this is just great.
Now he's really like a
giant monster, Luffy.
Stop it, Luffy.
You're destroying your own crew!
I'm kinda in a hurry here, okay?
What do you want with me?
Yeah, sorry to bug you like this, but
this is really important, I promise.
We'll only take a second of your time.
We've been looking all
over the place for you.
You're our only hope.
They call the two of
us the Risky Brothers.
The gang here is the Rolling Pirates.
And our captain is Lola, the Proposer.
You want to get back to the mansion
pronto so you can beat up Gecko Moria?
Right, pal?
Yeah, that's right Now could you
tell me what you want with me?
Listen, you're in luck.
Because we just happen to know
the secret to taking out Moria!
We can give you the power to do it, too.
And all you gotta do
is kick his ass for us.
What are you, a secret?
Give me power? Yep.
Seriously, who the hell are you guys?
Allow us to introduce you to the captain
of the Rolling Pirates, Lola the Proposer.
Current proposal count 4,443.
Oh, my, aren't you handsome.
Will you marry me? No, thanks.
Rejected!
That's 4,444!
Better luck next time!
Anyway,
Moria took all the
Rolling Pirate's shadows,
so we're stuck wandering this
forest till someone gets him back.
Yeah, well, he took my shadow, too.
That's why I'm in a hurry.
I won't take no for an
answer, Straw Hat Luffy.
You're a hero.
In all of Thriller Bart's history,
nobody has been able to
wreak as much havoc as you.
You walloped the Mysterious Three,
returned some of the stolen shadows,
and caused tons of property damage.
We've had nothing but
misery in this crappy
place till you showed up
and started kicking ass.
On the downside, it's kind of your fault
that they brought Oars back to life.
That maybe wasn't so great.
We have a whole network of victims, so
we know everything that's going on here.
We've been stuck here without
our shadows for three years.
I don't want to spend the rest
of my life on this stupid ship.
If you guys beat Merde up for
us, we could all get out of here?
and finally see the sun
again after all this time.
But we've got another problem right now.
Merde is making things
even tougher than usual.
You know where the bastard's at?
He's camped out inside
Orr's stomach. No way!
Did Orr's eat Moria? It's complicated.
He's in there piloting him like a ship.
Anyway, the point is, you're going to have
to take out that giant with your shadow.
Otherwise, you won't be able
to lay a finger on Moria.
But I figure you would
want to beat him anyway,
since he's giving your crew a
pounding out in the courtyard.
Are you serious?
Damn it, I gotta help
them before it's too late!
Not so fast!
Just sit tight for one second
and we'll show you our trick.
Trust me, you are gonna love this!
All right, boys, bring out the shadow!
Roger!
Stay out of the way!
Shadow's coming through!
Hm?
You can grab them?
Once they're separated, yeah.
When you feed the zombies a little
bit of salt and they come flying out,
you can just nab them out of the air
with your bare hands, no problem.
Hee-ho! Ah!
What are you doing?!
Stay still!
Stop it!
I feel like I'm gonna die!
All right it's in so how is it you
didn't lose consciousness did you
I'm fine all right i guess that's
a start can you use a sword
No not as far as i know bring the sword
Wait, how did I do that?
It's quite simple.
The shadow we just
stuffed inside you used to
belong to a powerful
swordsman from the Navy.
It's like Moria did with my shadow.
Yeah, but since you're still alive, it adds
the shadow's fighting power to your own.
The point is, as long
as you don't pass out,
we can stuff as many
shadows in you as we got.
Ever since we figured out Moria's powers,
we've been waiting for the
chance to turn them against him.
With a little boost,
you'll be unstoppable.
We still have a whole
bunch of shadows left, too.
As long as you're tough
enough to withstand them,
we can give you as many as you want?
and your power will grow with each one.
Okay, but why do you have so
many shadows in the first place?
The idea was to purify a bunch of
zombies and find our own shadows,
not collect them.
But even if we didn't
know who they belonged to,
it didn't seem right to
leave them with the zombies.
So we thought, what the hell, might
as well take them back with us.
There's one important thing you've
got to remember about this, though.
As you know, putting a shadow
in a corpse makes a zombie.
But if your body still has a soul,
the shadow won't stick around.
You'll only be powered
up for about ten minutes.
After that, all the shadows fly out
and go back to their original owners.
You got it, pal?
Just ten minutes, sink or swim.
We'll give you every shadow we nab,
so you should be pretty
powerful when we're done.
That's a lot!
Shadows are not the fogs clearing up.
We only have about 20 minutes before the
sun rises and roasts all of us anyway.
Our lives are in your hands.
Steal your mind, Straw Hat.
When we tried this trick before,
we could only handle two
or three shadows ourselves.
But you should be able to
do 20 or 30, no problem.
Go for it, boys!
I didn't agree to this!
They're really slow down!
I had no idea this was possible.
I've never seen anyone with
so much willpower before.
Now I know he can do it.
He can beat Moria! Whoa!
That's all of him!
He took all 100 shadows! Unbelievable!
Uh, hey, buddy, you doing
okay with all those shadows?
Still feeling like yourself?
You're still Straw Hat Luffy, right?
Oh, yeah.
It's me.
I'm getting stronger and stronger.
I can feel it.
He seems kind of different, you know?
I mean, it's not my imagination, is it?
Because I'm pretty sure
he used to be smaller.
It's beautiful.
I feel like I want to propose
to him all over again.
They all want to fight.
The shadows want to fight now!
Then let them go wild.
Hurry, there's not much time.
Just ten minutes to show
Moria the meaning of terror.
It's time to escape from this hell.
Now get going, Nightmare Loopy!
I'm coming for you, Moria!
Hey, come back!
The mansion's the other way!
Here it comes!
This whole stretching
thing makes fighting fun!
Come back!
What the hell's going on here?
He just got exponentially more powerful.
It's not like he ate a Devil Fruit,
so how's he able to stretch like that?
It's gotta be Mario.
What did he do?
There you have it.
Now you know the nightmarish
power of the Shadow Shadow Fruit.
Shadow Revolution.
Revolution?
A shadow is a helpless prisoner
to the body that casts it,
mimicking it like a reflection.
The body and shadow are physically
fused to the same shapes and movements.
It's a basic law of nature.
But I freed Oz's shadow
from the dominance of Oz's
body and taken control of
its form with my own shadow.
I can now change the shape
of Oz's shadow as I wish,
thereby forcing Oz's body to match
and follow its every contortion.
As I said,
it's long-natured that the body and
shadow must always hold the same shape.
But now the shadow is no longer
the subordinate, but the master.
The body is forced to obey
any shape the shadow takes.
This is the power of shadow revolution.
Moria is even stronger than we thought.
Even if Oz doesn't have a double
fruit power, he can still stretch.
If Moria controls his shadow,
he can rewrite the rules.
It's a bit of cold comfort to know
that Orz isn't actually a rubber man.
If he has all the same powers,
it doesn't do us much good.
Wasn't he tough enough already?
I mean, give us a break here.
Right?
It was hard before, but
now it's almost impossible.
You know, he has even more
tricks than Straw Hat.
For example, if I force
his shadow into a ball...
Orz will become a ball as well!
Oh, Spawn!
Dodge this. Roll!
Um... Okay.
Huh?
Come on, Master.
What's the big idea here, huh?
This is my fight.
I should get to try. Kashi!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interfere.
I'll just focus on assisting from here on.
And now, crush each one of
them however you see fit.
Get back here, Zoro!
Don't be reckless!
Hey, this just occurred
to me, but where is Luffy?
He ran off after Moria
and got tricked somehow.
I'm sure he's going to
be back soon, though!
Seriously?
Does he have to do
something stupid every time?
What should I do?
Oh,
it probably won't help if
I tell them another one
of the seven warlords is
somewhere on the island.
I'll get to that later.
Okay, I know I'm a little late to the
party, but let me get this straight.
Are you saying we've got
to defeat Luffy, Zombie,
and Moria if we want to get
everyone's shadows back?
Is that the gist of it?
Yeah, that's about it. You're kidding!
The sun is almost up!
The enemy is forcing our hand here.
It's not like we have much of a choice!
Excuse me! Huh?
The skeleton?
I didn't know you were here, too.
I beg of you.
Please, allow me to help.
I have an idea that just might work.
My friends, I appreciate your trust in me.
I don't think it should be
too tough to pull it off.
Are you sure about this, Brooke?
I'm not trying to talk
you out of it or anything,
but you saw what happened to Franky,
right?
Don't blame me if
anything goes wrong, okay?
But if this is what you
want, I'm glad to help.
Now, Dark Cloud Tempo!
I'm ready fire at will i can't
believe we're using this thing again?
There's one thing i fear more than
death being unable to repay my debts.
I'll fight to the last bone you can
count on me right try not to die!
I'm getting such a shock
that I can see my bones!
Well, I was only bones to begin with.
All right, here I come, like an
arrow, forced with lightning!
Lightning bones!
Come on, bone them all!
It worked!
He shot straight through him!
There's a hole in me! Now's our chance!
Follow-up attack!
As they say, mission accomplished.
Nice work there, Bones!
All right, two-sword style.
Tower climb!
You bastard!
You're next!
But first, that skeleton's
gonna pay for hurting me!
Go, go!
Oh, no!
He's going after Brock! Relax!
Brock, no! Skeleton!
Take this!
Atlas Comet!
Didn't work!
Oh, crap.
Keep fighting, Usopp!
Hey, what about you?
You just made yourself next, long-nosed.
Your friend with the swords can wait!
I'm a dead man!
Why can't I stretch?
Tochente fleur, Katorea manos.
Where'd all these hands come from?
That's cheating!
Give it up, or I'll snap your neck!
Your shadow revolution is over!